jobsalert.pk 2019-10-17

# Privacy & Policy | Jobs in Pakistan

You do not have to give us personal information to visit JobsAlert.PK. If you choose to provide us with additional information through an e-mail message, inquiry form, comments, etc., we will only maintain the information as long as needed to respond to your question, inquiry, or to fulfill the stated purpose of the communication. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not give, share, sell or transfer any personal information to a third party.

**Website Traffic Analysis Software  
**

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. We also monitor our traffic to analyze visitors’s information, such as, but not limited to, operating system, browsers, screen resolutions and similar information.

In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.

**E-mail Newsletters**

If users wish to subscribe to our e-mail newsletters, we ask for contact information. Our newsletters are powered by JetPack. We and JetPack use information submitted by you in the same manner as we use contact information described above. Recipients of our newsletters can unsubscribe using the instructions listed at the end of the e-mail newsletter.

**Third Party Advertising Partners**

All users of JobsAlert.PK must keep in mind that third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browsers, or using web beacons to collect information as a result of ad servings on JobsAlert.PK.

For instance, Google uses the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.google.com/doubleclick/) on JobsAlert.PK for displaying AdSense for content ads. Similarly, other advertising partners may use their respective cookies to track advertising stats.

**External Links**

Our web sites contains links to other sites. JobsAlert.PK is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each web site to which we may link that may collect personal information.

**Disclaimer for  ** **Use of Website Materials**

All content, design, text, logos, sound, images, graphics, and the selection and arrangement thereof, and all other elements of the JobsAlert.PK Web Site are the sole and exclusive property of JobsAlert.PK, and are protected by copyright, intellectual property, trade dress and other applicable laws and may not be copied, modified, published, imitated, distributed, or transmitted in whole or in part without the prior written consent of JobsAlert.PK.

Please report any such instances of misuse to info@jobsalert.pk

**Disclaimer for Press Releases:**

JobsAlert.pk receives many press releases from PR Agencies, companies, media partners and other parties. We do do not accept any responsibility for the accuracy and completeness of the information provided in the press releases.

We reserve the right to make necessary changes in any PR (if required) and we also reserve the right to reject or remove old PRs anytime without advanced notice.

**Note:**  The contents of our Privacy Policy are subject to change.
